<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bakmi GM</string>
    <string name="nikmati">Enjoy attractive offers, points and more with the exclusive Bakmi Gmania prize program. Sign up now!</string>
    <string name="gabung">Join Now</string>
    <string name="pilihbhs">" Language Choices"</string>
    <string name="tullisanbakmigm">Bakmi GM</string>
    <string name="indo">Indonesian</string>
    <string name="ing">English</string>
    <string name="main">" Game"</string>
    <string name="not">" Notification"</string>
    <string name="gbgmember">Become a Member</string>
    <string name="tan">" Question"</string>
    <string name="sya">" Terms and Conditions"</string>
    <string name="syagm">Bakmi GM Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="kebijak">" Privacy policy"</string>
    <string name="hbg">Contact us</string>
    <string name="addre">Address</string>
    <string name="mail">" E-mail"</string>
    <string name="bkmimail">help@bgmania.bakmigm.com</string>
    <string name="keterangan1">Users of the Bakmi GM Application agree to and accept the terms of use of the Application as can be revised by Bakmi GM from time to time, and constitutes a binding agreement between the User and Bakmi GM. By downloading or installing the Bakmi GM Application, the User acknowledges and agrees to be bound by these terms. If the User does not agree to these terms, the User does not agree to these Terms, the User cannot use this Bakmi GM Application.</string>
    <string name="keterangan2">Bakmi GM develops this application as it should and the user bears all the risks of using this Application. Bakmi GM has the right to display various promotions and all forms of advertising implicitly and explicitly as long as it is still in the legal channels without asking approval or giving compensation to the user.</string>
    <string name="ket2">" Bakmi GM is not responsible for costs, damage and defects caused, process failures, interruptions, length of operation and transitions, viruses or connection failures caused by the performance of the 2nd or 3rd party. Bakmi GM is not responsible for losses arising from loss or in the event of theft of user information sent or stored on the device or originating from unauthorized transactions or fraud related to the Application. Applications and Content are protected by copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, law and other proprietary rights, and may also have a security component that protects digital information as permitted by Bakmi GM or the Content owner."</string>
    <string name="ket3">Bakmi GM gives users personal licenses that are non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited and can be canceled to use the Application to use the application for personal and non-commercial use found on non-tablet and iphone android devices. This application is owned and controlled by users who comply with Apple\'s and Google\'s provisions.</string>
    <string name="ket4">Bakmi GM does not permit any party to use the application in any other way, without limitation, buying and selling of applications, transfer, modification or distribution of applications or text, images, music, barcodes, videos, hyperlink data, and content related to this application.</string>
    <string name="ket5">These provisions are subject to change and updates are made to the application for which new conditions will be published separately in other provisions.</string>
    <string name="ket6">If any provision of this provision is deemed unlawful, null or void for any reason it cannot be implemented, then the provision will be deemed separate from this provision and does not affect the validity and applicability of the remaining provisions.</string>
    <string name="ketmain">" Enjoy attractive offers, points and more with the exclusive Bakmi GMania prize program. Sign up now!"</string>
    <string name="boldguna">Recommended Application Use</string>
    <string name="ketguna">The User has agreed that the use of this Application and any Content must comply with this Application and any Content must comply with the provisions and policies made by Bakmi GM. Users are prohibited from using this application to:</string>
    <string name="ketguna1">1. Harassing, abusing, lurking, threatening, polluting good pests or violating public rights or other ownership rights.</string>
    <string name="ketguna2">" 2. Violating applicable law in Indonesia."</string>
    <string name="ketguna3">3. Commit fraud using this Application.</string>
    <string name="ketguna4">4. Use or launch any automated system such as robots, spiders, or Offline readers to access this Application.</string>
    <string name="ketguna5">5. Entering a virus or computer code, files or programs that will interfere with the application process or the functionality that is owned by the application and interfere with the work conduciveness of mobile phone devices.</string>
    <string name="boldinden">Identification</string>
    <string name="ketinden">The user agrees to take responsibility, compensate for damages, pay fines, for all claims, claims, damages, fines and obligations that have been caused by the user of the Application to Bakmi GM. Bakmi GM has the right to plea and exclusive control over all issues involving compensation by users of the Application. If the user violates the intellectual property rights owned by PT. Griya Miesejati, Apple Inc., and Google LLC, the user will be fully responsible for the Act and will be willing to investigate, defend and resolve cases of intellectual property violations that occur.</string>
    <string name="sanggah">Refutation</string>
    <string name="lisen">" User License"</string>
    <string name="pisah">Severability</string>
    <string name="terima">I accept the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="next">" Continue"</string>
    <string name="tanggung">Responsible</string>
    <string name="kettanggung">" Bakmi GM is responsible to the user for the use of the application in connection with the following matters:"</string>
    <string name="kettanggung1">" 1. Member Point"</string>
    <string name="kettanggung11">" o Point members who do not enter the member account more than 1 X 24 hours after the member makes a transaction. Bakmi GM will only process member complaints if Bakmi GM receives a complaint not included from the member via email help@bgmania.bakmigm.com which is accompanied by a proof of receipt of the shopping receipt."</string>
    <string name="kettanggung12">o Pointed member deducted when exchanging vouchers that did not work due to system failure. Only applies to members whose points have been deducted but have not yet gotten a voucher code.</string>
    <string name="kettanggung2">2. Member transactions that are not recorded in the system due to the proven result of GM\'s Bakmi negligence to enter the member Mobile number that has been registered on the shopping receipt. Bakmi GM will replace member points after receiving a report from the member accompanied by proof of receipt.</string>
    <string name="kettanggung3">" 3. Member transactions that are not recorded on the system even though they have entered the member number on the shopping receipt. Transactions and points will be processed into the system as a Bakmi GM member right."</string>
    <string name="kettanggung4">" 4. Bakmi GM's liability is limited to the replacement of vouchers or customer points."</string>
    <string name="appli">" Application and Content"</string>
    <string name="ketappli">" The application and all contents contained therein are protected by copyright, trademark, patent and trade secret, international agreements, law and other ownership rights, and also have a security component that protects digital information as Bakmi GM determines."</string>
    <string name="ubah">Change</string>
    <string name="ketubah">Bakmi GM has the right to add, subtract and change the terms of the applicable provisions relating to the use of the Application at any time in accordance with Bakmi GM\'s policy by changing its Privacy Policy on the Application, the User has the right to continue to use and utilize the application as appropriate.</string>
    <string name="bijakgm">" Bakmi GM Privacy Policy"</string>
    <string name="ketbijakgm1">Using the Bakmi GM Application and providing us with your personal data means that you have accepted everything that applies in this Privacy Statement. We ask that you do not submit your personal data if you do not agree with some or all of the contents of these Privacy Conditions.</string>
    <string name="ketbijakgm2">Bakmi GM has the right to change this Privacy Statement periodically. We recommend that you read this privacy statement periodically to ensure that this privacy policy is what you want and how your personal data will be processed.</string>
    <string name="kumpul">Data collection</string>
    <string name="ket1kumpul">Mobile Application users provide personal data to Bakmi GM voluntarily which includes:</string>
    <string name="ket1kumpul1">" 1. Information you provided when registering"</string>
    <string name="ket1kumpul2">" 2. Information we get when you complete your profile on the application"</string>
    <string name="ket1kumpul3">3. Information we get from you when you use the Application or when you make transactions at the Bakmi GM Store</string>
    <string name="ket1kumpul4">4. Information we get from other sources.</string>
    <string name="ket2kumpul">The data requested to register is Name, Mobile Number, Date of Birth, Gender, Address and other personal data that support the operational process in this application.</string>
    <string name="ket3kumpul">In addition to Name, Mobile Number, Date of Birth, Gender, and Address the user has the right to choose to fill in other personal data. However, this will make a difference to the service or information that will be obtained between users who do not complete their personal data. Information related to personal data sent to this application is not traded or submitted to parties not involved in the operation of this application.</string>
    <string name="bagidata">" How We Share Your Data"</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata">There are a number of situations where we will share your data with others, namely:</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata1">" 1. To the service providers for marketing purposes"</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata11">Our third party, which provides services and develops our application system, holds and owns your data for promotional purposes, events or other marketing activities for you.</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata2">2. Business Transactions</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata21">If we do a joint venture or other situation that causes us to have to provide our entire company data including your data.</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata3">3. When you use our application, third parties can view data and information about you through cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies, information that can be obtained is the type of device you are using, your operating system, your browser, and your internet operator.</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata4">4. We will share your information if we believe in good faith that access, use, store or disclose information is used to:</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata41">• When needed to provide your data for purposes that can protect the rights and obligations of companies and consumers in accordance with applicable law.</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata42">" • Comply with laws, regulations, legal processes that apply at the request of the State apparatuses that must be fulfilled."</string>
    <string name="ket1bagidata43">• Detecting, preventing or handling security fraud or technical problems</string>
    <string name="aman">Data Security</string>
    <string name="ketaman">" Bakmi GM performs actions deemed necessary to ensure user data is safe, protected and controlled in accordance with applicable company regulations to ensure that there is no risk of loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to your data."</string>
    <string name="ubahprivate">Changes to Privacy Provisions</string>
    <string name="ketubahprivate">" We will change this privacy policy from time to time. We will reduce your rights to this privacy policy without your explicit consent. We also recommend that you continue to read our privacy terms in order to adjust to the privacy conditions that we will continue to update."</string>
    <string name="kethbgbijak">" Please contact us if you have questions, comments and criticisms and suggestions. You can contact us by email at help@bgmania.bakmigm.com."</string>
    <string name="masukbold">" LOG IN"</string>
    <string name="nohp">No. HP</string>
    <string name="dftar">" List"</string>
    <string name="nmdpn">" First name*"</string>
    <string name="nmblkg">" Last name*"</string>
    <string name="tgllhr">Date of birth*</string>
    <string name="wlyahregis">Registration Area *</string>
    <string name="tk">Choice Store *</string>
    <string name="tkaja">" Store"</string>
    <string name="nmdepan">" First name"</string>
    <string name="namablkng">" Last name"</string>
    <string name="dmy">DD-MM-YYYY</string>
    <string name="wilayahhh">" Enter the Registration Territory"</string>
    <string name="kadotulis">Complete the profile and get a chance to play the wheel again to win attractive prizes</string>
    <string name="Katalog">Katalog</string>
    <string name="Hadiah">My gift</string>
    <string name="AP">Management profile</string>
    <string name="LEWAT">" skip over"</string>
</resources>